# NANDANA S

## Web Developer



#### +91 8921189997



Thrissur

#### SKILLS

- PYTHON
- HTML
- CSS
- DJANGO
- My sql
- WORDPRESS

## **EDUCATION**

HOLY FAMILY CGHS SCHOOL
CHEMBUKAVU THRISSUR
SSLC 2017 - 2018
HOLY FAMILY CGHS SCHOOL
CHEMBUKAVU THRISSUR
HIGHER SECONDARY 2018 - 2020
VIMALA COLLEGE (AUTONOMOUS)
THRISSUR BVOC WEB TECHNOLOGY
2020 - 2023

## ABILITY

- Time management
- Teamwork
- Creativity
- Responsibility

#### PROFILE

Seeking a beginner role to enhance and explore my technical knowledge gained at CALICUT UNIVERSITY KERALA in the last three years. I hold a BACHELOR OF VOCATIONAL Degree from VIMALA COLLEGE (AUTONOMOUS) THRISSUR and won the quiz challenge held at the campus.

#### EXPERIENCE

Nyeste Venture Technologies Pvt, Ltd 12/10/2021 - 12/11/2021 Star Innovations Thrissur 05/05/2022 - 05/06/2022 Unique Occasion Tech 11/12/2022 - 30/03/2023 Up2 Tech (UI desginer) 01/06/2023- 20/08/2023

## **PROJECTS**

#### ·Internship and Project

Website Topic : SONA (hotel search) Server : Xampp Database : MySQL

Framework : Django Database Tool : PyCharm

#### ·Mini Project/Internship

Website Topic: Hot Duck Wok(chinese

restaurant) Server: wampserver

Database: MySQL Framework: Bootstrap

#### ·Mini Project/Internship

Topic: KENDAL (cosmetics)

Server: wampserver Database: MySQL Framework: Bootstrap